Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- School Work, 1949-1969; 5
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (3 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (4 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (5 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (6 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (7 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (8 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Articles: (1 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 16)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Articles: (2 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 17)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Articles: (3 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 18)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Articles: (4 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 19)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Articles: (5 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 20)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Articles: (6 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 21)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Rules: (1 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 22)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Rules: (2 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 23)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Rules: (3 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 150, Folder 24)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Rules: (4 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Rules: (5 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Notebook: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion: Rules: (6 of 6), 1968-1969 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Notebook: “Religion and Politics”: (1 of 3), undated (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Notebook: “Religion and Politics”: (2 of 3), undated (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Notebook: “Religion and Politics”: (3 of 3), undated (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Notes: Quotes: (1 of 4), undated (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Notes: Quotes: (2 of 4), undated (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Notes: Quotes: (3 of 4), undated (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Notes: Quotes: (4 of 4), undated (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Notes: Religious: (1 of 2), undated (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Notes: Religious: (2 of 2), undated (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Notes: Thesis: (1 of 2), undated (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Notes: Thesis: (1 of 2), undated (Box 151, Folder 14)
  - Essay: “A Problem in Wheeler Robinson’s Doctrine of Revelation”: (1 of 2), undated (Box 151, Folder 15)
  - Essay: “A Problem in Wheeler Robinson’s Doctrine of Revelation”: (2 of 2), undated (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - Essay: “An Exegesis of Romans 3:21-26: (1 of 3), 1957 January 15 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - Essay: “An Exegesis of Romans 3:21-26: (2 of 3), 1957 January 15 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - Essay: “An Exegesis of Romans 3:21-26: (3 of 3), 1957 January 15 (Box 151, Folder 19)
  - Essay: “Anselm”, undated (Box 151, Folder 20)
  - Essay: “Cajetan”, 1959 December 17 (Box 151, Folder 21)
  - Essay: “Christ as Head of the Church”: (1 of 2), 1960 May (Box 151, Folder 22)
  - Essay: “Christ as Head of the Church”: (2 of 2), 1960 May (Box 151, Folder 23)
  - Essay: “Comparative Semite Religions”, 1949 May 16 (Box 151, Folder 24)
  - Essay: “Differentiation and Undifference”, undated (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (1 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (2 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (3 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (4 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (5 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (6 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (7 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Colossians”: (8 of 8), 1956 Spring (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (1 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (2 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (3 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (4 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (5 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (6 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (7 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Essay: “Exegesis of Philippians”: (8 of 8), 1955 Fall (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Essay: Greek Philosophy: “5 Projects”: (1 of 3), 1953 November 20 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Essay: Greek Philosophy: “5 Projects”: (2 of 3), 1953 November 20 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Essay: Greek Philosophy: “5 Projects”: (3 of 3), 1953 November 20 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Essay: “John Calvin”, undated (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Essay: “Karl Barth’s Doctrine of Revelation”, undated (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - Essay: “Life and Thought of St. Bonaventura”: (1 of 2), 1954 February 19 (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - Essay: “Life and Thought of St. Bonaventura”: (2 of 2), 1954 February 19 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Essay: “Luther’s Conception of Faith”, 1960 November 28 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Essay: “Medieval Christian Philosophy”, 1959 December 3 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Essay: “Meister Eckhart”, 1960 January 12 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Essay: “Metaphysics”, 1953-1954 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Essay: “Paul’s Doctrine of Election”, 1954 January 27 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Essay: “Personalism of Flewelling”, 1954 January 27 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Essay: Philosophy: “Problems”: (1 of 2), 1953 October 22 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Essay: Philosophy: “Problems”: (2 of 2), 1953 October 22 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Essay: “Philosophy of Brand Blanshard”: (1 of 2), 1954 February 26 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Essay: “Philosophy of Brand Blanshard”: (2 of 2), 1954 February 26 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Essay: “Positivism and/or Philosophy”: (1 of 3), 1954 May 17 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Essay: “Positivism and/or Philosophy”: (2 of 3), 1954 May 17 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Essay: “Positivism and/or Philosophy”: (3 of 3), 1954 May 17 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Essay: “Religion and the Christian Faith”, undated (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Essay: “Roman Stoicism”, 1957 April 16 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Essay: “Sources of Thomas Aquinas’ Doctrine of God”: (1 of 3), 1959 Fall (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Essay: “Sources of Thomas Aquinas’ Doctrine of God”: (2 of 3), 1959 Fall (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Essay: “Sources of Thomas Aquinas’ Doctrine of God”: (3 of 3), 1959 Fall (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Essay: “The Council of Arles”: (1 of 6), 1956 April 5 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Essay: “The Council of Arles”: (2 of 6), 1956 April 5 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - Essay: “The Council of Arles”: (3 of 6), 1956 April 5 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - Essay: “The Council of Arles”: (4 of 6), 1956 April 5 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - Essay: “The Council of Arles”: (5 of 6), 1956 April 5 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - Essay: “The Council of Arles”: (6 of 6), 1956 April 5 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - Essay: “The Downward Pull and the Transformed Mind”, 1956 October 26 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Essay: “The Ethic of Love”: (1 of 2), 1954 November 5 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Essay: “The Ethic of Love”: (2 of 2), 1954 November 5 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Essay: “The First Epistle of John”: (1 of 2), 1955 Spring (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Essay: “The First Epistle of John”: (2 of 2), 1955 Spring (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Essay: “The Freedom of Constraint”, 1956 January 11 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Essay: “The Person of Christ in Hebrews”, 1952 Fall (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Essay: “The Quest of the Historical Jesus”, 1954 December 10 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Essay: “The Southern Baptist Convention during the Civil War”: (1 of 2), 1957 May 14 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Essay: “The Southern Baptist Convention during the Civil War”: (2 of 2), 1957 May 14 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Essay: “Time”, 1954 February 22 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Essay: “Whitehead’s Critique of Traditional Theology”: (1 of 2), 1960 January 26 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Essay: “Whitehead’s Critique of Traditional Theology”: (2 of 2), 1960 January 26 (Box 154, Folder 13)
- Sermons, 1954-1968; 6
  General condition: Unknown.
  This series contains sermons, outlines, addresses, and notes written by Tracy Early. It is comprised primarily of radio addresses and sermons. Tracy Early broadcasted devotionals across the airwaves for WDDY Gloucester from 1954 to 1967 and preached at Urbanna Baptist Church in Virginia from 1964 to 1968. The materials have been organized both by type and chronologically. Sermons have been identified according to the scripture reference.
  - Programs, 1959-1966, undated (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Clippings: The Baptist Program, 1959 August (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Obituaries, 1965-1967 September 9 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Obituaries, 1967 September 10-1968 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Notes, undated (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - Radio Devotionals: 1 Thessalonians 1:2-3, 1954 February 28 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Radio Devotionals: “Responsibilities of Parents”, 1955 June 6 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Radio Devotionals: “Responsibilities of Parents”, 1955 June 7 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Radio Devotionals: “Responsibilities of Parents”, 1955 June 8 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - Radio Devotionals: “Responsibilities of Parents”, 1955 June 9 (Box 154, Folder 24)
  - Radio Devotionals: Genesis 1, 1956 March 15 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Radio Devotionals: Ephesians 1:5-6, Psalms 143, 1964 May 5, 12 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Radio Devotionals: Psalm 32, James 1, 1964 July 7, 14 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Radio Devotionals: Romans 5, Hebrews 4, 1964 July 21, September 8 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Radio Devotionals: Hebrews 11, Proverbs 1, 1964 November 25, 1965 January 5 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Radio Devotionals: Proverbs 22, Isaiah 55, 1965 January 19, March 8 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Radio Devotionals: Isaiah 53, Psalm 8, 1965 March 16, May 11 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Radio Devotionals: Matthew 21, Matthew 24, 1965 July 13, 20 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Radio Devotionals: Romans 12, Romans 13, 1965 September 14, 21 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Radio Devotionals: Psalm 95, Matthew 6, 1965 November 16-17 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Radio Devotionals: Hebrews 2, 4, 8, 1966 January 5, 19, March 2 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Radio Devotionals: Hebrews 9, Matthew 5, 1966 March 10, May 3 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Radio Devotionals: Psalm 33, 46, 104, 1966 July 4, 26, September 13 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - Radio Devotionals: 1 John 1-3, 1967 January 9-11 (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - Radio Devotionals: 1 John 4-5, 1967 January 12-13 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - Radio Devotionals: Genesis 1, Hebrews 10, 1967 October 9, undated (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - Addresses: Religious, 1964-1965 January (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Addresses: Religious, 1965 June-1966 August (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Addresses: Religious, 1966 September-1968 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - General, 1955 May 4-August 14 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - General, 1955 August 17-1956 March 23 (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - General, 1956 April 1-June 24 (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - General, 1956 July 1-October 21 (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - General, 1957 March 24-November 24 (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - General, 1957 December 1-1958 April 27 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - General, 1958 May 4-August 31 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - General, 1958 September 14-November 27 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - General, 1958 December 14-1959 April 26 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - General, 1959 May 3-1960 July 3 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - General, 1960 August 7-1961 December 24 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - General, 1962 July 1-November 25 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - General, 1962 December 2-1964 March 15 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - General, circa 1954-1962 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Luke 19, Luke 4, 1964 March 22, 29 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Matthew 5, John 1, 1964 April 5, 12 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Matthew 3, Ephesians 6, 1964 April 19, 26 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - 2 Timothy 2, Psalm 107, 1964 May 3, 10 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Acts 2, Leviticus 25, John 10, 1964 May 17, 24, 31 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - John 6, 18, 1964 June 7, 14 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - Luke 19, Matthew 10, 1964 June 21, 28 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Mark 10, Luke 5, 1964 July 5, 12 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - John 12, Jeremiah 1, 1964 July 19, 26 (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Jeremiah 2, 15, 1964 August 2, 19 (Box 156, Folder 19)
  - Jeremiah 17, 23, 1964 August 16, 23 (Box 156, Folder 20)
  - Jeremiah 29, 31, 1964 August 30, September 6 (Box 156, Folder 21)
  - 2 Corinthians 4, 1 Peter 1, 1964 September 20, 27 (Box 156, Folder 22)
  - 1 Peter 1, 2, 1964 October 4, 11 (Box 156, Folder 23)
  - 1 Peter 2, 3, 1964 October 18, 25 (Box 156, Folder 24)
  - 1 Peter 4, 1964 November 1, 8 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - 1 Peter 5, 1964 November 15, 22 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Psalm 136, Luke 1, 1964 November 26, 29 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Luke 2, 1964 December 6, 20, 27 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Luke 4, 5, 1965 January 3, 10, 17 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Luke 6, 7, 8, 1965 January 31, February 7, 14 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Luke 9, 10, 1965 February 21, 28, March 7, 14 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Luke 17, 18, 1965 March 21, 28 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Philippians 4, Luke 24, 1965 April 4, 18 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Romans 1, 2, 1965 April 25, May 2, 9 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Romans 3, 1965 May 16, 23 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Galatians 5, Romans 4, 5, 1965 June 6, 13, 20 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Romans 6, 7, 1965 June 27, July 4, 11 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Romans 7, 8, 1965 July 18, 25, August 1 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Romans 9, 1965 August 8, 15 (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - Romans 10, 11, 1965 August 22, 29 (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - Romans 11, 12, 1965 September 5, 12 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Romans 13, 14, 15, 1965 September 19, 26, October 3 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Matthew 6, Psalm 95, 2 Timothy 4, 1965 October 10, 17, 24 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Isaiah 56, 1 Corinthians 11, 1965 October 31, November 7 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - 1 Chronicles 16, Isaiah 6, John 1, 1965 November 14, 21, 28 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - 1 Corinthians, Isaiah 40, Hebrews 1, 1965 December 12, 19, 26 (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Hebrews 2, 3, 1966 January 2, 9 (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Hebrews 4, 5, 1966 January 16, 23 (Box 157, Folder 24)
  - Hebrews 6, 7, 1966 February 6, 20 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Hebrews 8, 9, 1966 February 27, March 6 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Hebrews 10, 11, 1966 March 13, 20 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Hebrews 12, Matthew 27, 1966 March 27, April 8 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - 1 Corinthians 1, Hebrews 13, John 3, 1966 April 10, 17, 24 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Matthew 5, 1 Corinthians 13, John 13, 1966 May 1, 8, 15 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Galatians 5, Psalm 1, 2, 1966 May 22, June 5, 12 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Psalm 8, 15, 16, 23, 1966 June 19, 26, July 3 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Psalm 24, 1966 July 10 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Psalm 32, 46, 51, 1966 July 17, 24, 31 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Psalm 73, 90, 104, 1966 August 7, 14, 28 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Psalm 105, 115, 139, 1966 September 4, 11, 18 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Psalm 145, Matthew 5, 1966 September 25, October 9 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Mark 10, Acts 10, 1966 October 16, 23 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Galatians 5, Isaiah 65, 1966 October 30, November 6 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - 1 Peter 2, Job 31, Isaiah 43, 1966 November 13, 20, 27 (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - Isaiah 11, 6, Luke 2, 1966 December 4, 18, 25 (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - Isaiah 43, Acts 6, Mark 1, 1967 January 8, 15, 29 (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Mark 2, 3, 4, 1967 February 5, 12, 19 (Box 158, Folder 19)
  - Mark 5, 6, 1967 February 26, March 5 (Box 158, Folder 20)
  - Mark 8, 16, 1967 March 12, 26 (Box 158, Folder 21)
  - Acts 1, 4, 1967 April 2, 9 (Box 158, Folder 22)
  - Acts 5, 7, 1967 April 16, 23 (Box 158, Folder 23)
  - Acts 8, Exodus 14, 1967 April 30, May 7 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Acts 10, 13, 1967 May 14, 21 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Acts 15, Genesis 1, 2, 1967 June 4, 11, 18 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Genesis 3, 4, 1967 June 25, July 2 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Genesis 6, 11, 1967 July 9, 16 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Genesis 12, 13, 1967 July 23, 30 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Genesis 15, 17, 1967 August 6, 13 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Genesis 22, 25, 1967 August 20, 27 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Genesis 26, 28, 1967 September 3, 10 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Genesis 32, 35, 1967 September 17, 24 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Genesis 37, 50, 1967 October 1, 8 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Ephesians 4, Mark 12, 1967 October 15, 22 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Matthew 23, Mark 14, 1967 October 29, November 5 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - 2 Timothy 4, Matthew 28, 1967 November 12, 19 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - 1 Corinthians 12, Matthew 1, 1967 November 26, December 3 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Matthew 2, Luke 2, 1967 December 17, 24 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Matthew 5, Isaiah 60, 1967 December 31, 1968 January 7 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Matthew 5, 1968 January 14, 21 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Matthew 5, 6, 1968 February 4, 11 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Matthew 6, 1968 February 18, 25 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Psalm 61, Matthew 7, 1968 March 3, 10 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Matthew 7, 1968 March 17, 24 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Matthew 7, 1968 March 31, April 7 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Matthew 7, Romans 15, 1968 April 14, 28 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Romans 16, Mark 10, 1968 May 5, 12 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Luke 19, 7, 1968 May 19, 26 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - John 20, 2 Timothy 1, 1968 June 16, 23 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - 2 Corinthians 7, Deuteronomy 8, Acts 4, 1968 June 30, July 7, 14 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Philippians 1, 1968 July 21, 28 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Philippians 2, 3, 4, 1968 August 4, 11, 18 (Box 160, Folder 15)
- Books, 1939-2004; 7
  This series contains an index citing all of the books belonging to the collection. Also
  included are photographs, clippings, and notes found within the pages of these books. Most of the books were gifts to Tracy Early and contain letters or acknowledgements to him. The majority of the books are available when searching on Bearcat. The notes are organized according to the author’s last name. If this is absent, then the title of the work is considered.
  - Index, undated (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Clippings: A World Without Hunger: J. Harry Haines, 1980 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: Cathedral of St. John, 1975-1996 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: The Human Encounter: Sheldon Ptaschevitch, 1969 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Clippings: Who’s Who in America, 1999 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Notes: Baylor Round-Up, 1951-1953 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Notes: Baylor Round-Up, 1954 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Notes: Cathedral of St. John: (1 of 4), 1973-2003, undated (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Notes: Cathedral of St. John: (2 of 4), 1973-2003, undated (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Notes: Cathedral of St. John: (3 of 4), 1973-2003, undated (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Notes: Cathedral of St. John: (4 of 4), 1973-2003, undated (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Notes: Encyclopedic Dictionary of Religion, 1979 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Notes: Television and Religion: William F. Fore, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Notes: Urbanna: Richard Genders, 1980 (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - Notes: Thy Will Be Done: Benedict J. Groeschel and Terrence L. Weber, 1985-1999 (Box 161, Folder 15)
  - Notes: Southern Churches in Crisis: Samuel S. Hill, Jr., 1967 (Box 161, Folder 16)
  - Notes: Can These Bones Live?: Robert S. Lecky and H. Elliot Wright, 1969 (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - Notes: Christian Faith & Public Policy: Arthur Simon, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - Notes: God and the Rhetoric of Sexuality: Phyllis Trible, 1978 (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - Notes: Texts of Terror: Phyllis Trible, 1982-1986 (Box 161, Folder 20)
  - Notes: Seeing for Ourselves: Katerina K. Whitley, 2001 (Box 161, Folder 21)
  - Notes: Speaking for Ourselves: Katerina K. Whitley, 1998-1999 (Box 161, Folder 22)
  - Notes: Walking the Way of Sorrows: Katerina K. Whitley, 1989 (Box 161, Folder 23)
  - Notes: Holy Company: H. Elliott Wright, 1984-1991 (Box 161, Folder 24)
  - Photographic Materials: Photos: Baylor University, 1952-1953 (Box 161, Folder 25)
  - Photographic Materials: Photos: Baylor Round-Up, 1954 (Box 161, Folder 26)
  - Bible: Tracy “Bill” Early, 1939 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Bible: Tracy Early, undated (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Simply Sharing: Tracy Early, 1980 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - The New Testament: Charles Williams, 1952 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Urbanna Baptist Church: Evelyn Q. Ryland, 2004 (Box 162, Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1947-2003; 8
  This series contains photographs of Tracy Early and friends. These photographs were not included in other series.
  - General, 1947-1948, 1950, 1952-1953 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - General, 1953-1954, 1956-1957 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - General, 1958-1959, 1963 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - General, 1964, 1967, 1977, 1979, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - General, 1985, 1989 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - General, 1991, 1993 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - General, 1993-1994 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - General, 1994-1995 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - General, 1995-1997 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - General, 1998-2001 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - General, 2001-2002 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - General, 2002-2003, undated (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - General, undated (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - General, undated (Box 163, Folder 14)
- Media, 1983-2000; 9
  General condition: Average.
  This series contains media, both audio and visual. There is a Department of Defense tape that has possible classified material. Two DVDs are of high school class reunions.
  - DOD Director 5200.30 17 Feb 83: 1 Film Reel, 1983 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - O’Connor 3/4/85: 1 Cassette Tape, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Snyder High School 1950 Class Reunion, 6 October 1990: 1 DVD (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Snyder High School 1950 Class Reunion, 2000: 1 DVD (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Shopping with Nancy: 1 DVD, undated (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Emilio Castro at Joan Campbell Install: 1 Cassette Tape, undated (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - 1 Magnetic Tape, undated (Box 164, Folder 7)
- Oversize, circa 1940s; 10
  This series contains oversized material that could not be included in other series. Copies of the scrap book pages can be seen in the Personal Material series.
  - Scrapbook #1, Circa 1940s (Box 165, Folder 1)